Once upon a time, Urashima Taro was taken into...
Undersea Palace of the Dragon King by the turtle he saved..
Hey, wai-!
The story we're gonna show to you kids now...
Make sure to only keep it between you and me.
Else, your face might become like this.
So y'all, please zip your mouths like this.
Let's Solve  the
Mystery of Urashima Taro
Brought to you by: Ko-FI.me/OrangeFlash
But we haven't received any signal from the spaceship.
Then, is it an UFO?
The signal sent back from the rocket is traced back to the earth.
We are further investigating, as we speak.
Now it is about to approach Earth.
Sir! We've traced the spacecraft from where the signal was sent.
Impossible!
The missing spaceship?
It is a miracle. a miraculous twist indeed.
I'm home, at last.
I had missed the earth for an year.
I made my family worry about me.
Congratulations!
Good job.
We have contacted your family on the earth.
Your son will be coming to pick you up, any moment from now.
Thank you. Sorry for making you worry.
Please help me land safely.
I want to meet my son whom I haven't seen for an year.
Dad.
Hmm...?
You are...
Impossible!
Dad, welcome home.
Well, I can't really blame you for being surprised.
After all, 1 year in space = 60 years on Planet Earth.
My son.
Dad.
Son.
Where is your mum?
She passed away 20 years ago.
Well? Did you like it?
How emotional!
But why didn't the pilot alone grew older?
When the moving speed of an object gets closer to the velocity of light
the time slows down.
That is to say, inside the rocket, the time will simply slow down.
No way!
Hey, Giant. Do you believe that?
Yeah, I believe it.
I was 1 hour late when I came out of the bullet train, after all.
Something like that.
But to be precise, It is the principle of relativity.
Correct.
A great scientist, Dr. Einstein wrote so.
You don't even know that?
Now I know.
Haven't y'all know the story of Urashima Taro?
Oh, in return for saving a Tortoise..
he feasted upon a banquet at the...
...Underwater Palace of the Dragon King.
Yeah and he received a Pandora's Box as a gift.
But when he opened it, he became an old man in an instant.
What a weird story.
Right, the 3 days in the...
Palace of the Dragon King = 300 years in the land world.
Really?
Then that must have been an account of Interstellar space travel...
The Tortoise must've been an Alien or something.
Then he rode on the interstellar spacecraft...
...which resembled a tortoise.
Because jumping into the sea without...
...wearing an oxygen tank, wouldn't make any sense and is impossible...
Then he was taken to the planet that looked like Dragon King's Palace.
You have a point, I see.
So you're telling me that the tale of Urashima Taro was...
...in fact an historical event?
Although it's a fairy tale, how romantic It'd be if it were to be true.
That's it!
Let's research and study about Urashima Taro.
Sounds interesting!
Let's do it as part of our summer vacation's group study.
We all agree!
So you see...
Please help us, Doraemon!
Time Machine or the Anywhere Door would do the job!
But it's just a fairy tale, and...
Urashima Taro might have never existed in reality, I think.
Just to be sure...
Oh, will you help us?
After I make a phone call.
To whom?
I 'd like to speak to the Time Investigation Corps and confirm!
Hello...
What? He really existed?
Yes, ok...
They said he existed...
In August 1049, he disappeared along side the coast.
And in the year 1349, he came home.
I knew it all along!
Doraemon, let's go ASAP.
Sure!
Destination: Year 1049!
I have brought my camera with me!
I want to take some memorable photos!
Why, of course you can!
Yayy!!!!
Year 1049, huh?
Somewhere along the coast...
There exists Urashima Taro...
Hey, that might be the tortoise from the legend.
Why Urashima Taro isn't here, yet?
He'll be here in no time.
Let me save it.
Hey, you can't change the history.
Ah. he comes.
That must be him.
That guy is Urashima Taro?
He is worse than I thought.
That is but history.
Hey, look! There he comes!
Hey, brats.
The historical moment.
What are you doing?
This Urashima Taro sure is rowdy!
The tortoise looks rather tasty.
Tasty?
If he eats the tortoise, the rest of the story will never happen.
Run.
Wait.
Excuse us!
What? You want to trade this tortoise with something else?
I haven't seen you before.
Are you kids' from the nearby village?
No...
How much money do you have with you?
Let's see...
¥1000.
¥1000?
That's all I have with me.
What is this paper?
You can't fool me!
You can't use this note as money in the year 1049.
Guess not.
Dora-chan, please help me buy the tortoise!
Though, I don't mind exchanging that shiny thing on your chest with this Tortoise.
No way, my Mum bought this broach for me.
So the deal's off!
Then forget about the Tortoise.
Wait, mister.
Shizuka-chan!
OK, tortoise, you can be rest assured now.
Be careful so that you won't get captured again by humans...
Shizuka-chan, will you become Urashima Taro?
No way, that'd be weird!
But you saved it!
But I'm a girl!
Then why don't you send it back to the sea, Doraemon?
I ain't a human being.
Giant?
I am Gouda Takeshi, not Urashima Taro.
What should we do?
It is different from the story.
Hey, it's getting away!
Wait...
We can't let you escape!
Our homework would be incomplete without you!
Hey, kids.
You must not trouble any living creature.
Let it go back to the sea.
Are you the real Urashima Taro?
So handsome.
OK, you can rest assured now.
You can go back to the sea.
You're just like how I imagined you to be!
Don't get caught by mischievous children ever again!
What? We troubled the tortoise?
Indeed.
Hey, what is it?
Hey, you can't run off on your own...
Do you know how much, the princess was worried about you?
Did you save the tortoise?
Oh, yes.
Tortoise is the Princess' pet.
We'd like to reward you.
Come on. Go aboard the ship please.
They left.
How can you let them just leave?
We've no choice but to follow them.
Let's see...
Not that, not this!
Found it! The Diving Airship.
This Diving Airship...
Explain about it later.
Yes...
Jump into it.
So the tortoise isn't an alien but a pet of the Princess Oto.
It is going to sink down.
So beautiful.
Palace of the Dragon King is located in the seabed.
But it is surprising that there is a submarine at this ancient era.
She might be an alien.
Even if Princess Oto is an alien, I can't wait to see her.
I want to feast upon the banquet.
That's so like you, Nobita-san!
But no one will ever believe that...
...we've been to Palace of the Dragon King.
But of course 'cause yer untrustworthy.
Hey...!
It's alright, I've brought my camera to take pictures.
The speed is being increased!
What is wrong?
I don't know. But the speed is very high.
5000 meters deep, 6000 meters...
Speed, speed...
Hey, I don't know.. Looks like we might time slip!
Wouldn't that break the Airship?
Don't worry, it can run on par with the speed of light.
It is tremendous.
We are going to get into the deep sea area.
It fades to dark.
What is this strange space?
It looks like we have slipped into an another dimension.
It seems as if we are floating.
I can't believe that a huge city lies at the ocean bed.
Maybe it is the Palace of the Dragon King.
Right, this is Palace of the Dragon King.
So beautiful.
We are going to crash land!
No.
I will die in the sea.
Doraemon! Mum!
Nobita... There is air, hmm...?
How come so?
What is going on here?
I don't know.
So this is the entrance to the Palace of the Dragon King.
Anyhow, we can't get inside..
I am going to take a photo for commemoration, say cheese!
OK? Here we go.
OK...
Are you the spies came from the land world?
Not really...
We come here just for our summer vacation study.
What, study...?
I arrest you for spying on our world.
Mum, I am scared...
We have been in jail for 3 days now.
Don't you have any gadget to escape from here?
Even I have no idea what's going on here..
So I don't know what to do!
For our research, we could have just did a study on rabbits or tortoise.
It is noisy outside.
Look... Urashima Taro is going home.
He has the Pandora's Box with him.
Damn, Urashima Taro feasted while we rot here...
Giant is right.
Plus he's got the box as gift.
Let us out.
Keep silence.
Now we are in meeting to discuss your punishment...
As spies, they must be killed.
This is but the eternal law.
They are but only minors.
But they must be punished...
What if they leak about our country, in the land world?
Then why did we let Urashima Taro go home?
He was given the Pandora's Box.
If he doesn't keep his mouth shut, he will become an old man.
President, what is the opinion of Princess Oto?
i don't want our princess to know about them...
We must decide how to punish them, on our own.
The sentence is out.
You all will be killed on the ground of being spies from the land world.
Damn.
Let me out.
I wanted to eat more Dorayaki.
No.
No!
Mum.
Damn it!
Silence.
Mr. president.
What now?
Please abort the spies' execution.
But why?
The judgement is already passed..
For the well-being and security of our country, there is no other choice.
However...
We found this picture after checking their camera.
These pictures prove that...
those kids are the ones who actually saved the tortoise.
Aim the target.
We are very sorry.
Please forgive us.
It's okay if you understand.
I was so scared.
Please enjoy your stay with us and Bon Appetite!
Yum!
How tasty!
This is why I love fairy tales.
You're such a glutton, so anything is tasty for you, Giant!
But how do you grow these tasty food here, all the way down in the seabed?
We use special techniques to grow our food here.
I'm curious. Are you the undersea race or an alien race?
Actually we used to live on land, a very long time ago.
But why do you live in undersea now?
Millions of years ago,
Our civilization was more technologically advanced than now.
Our country was located in the land world.
It was a beautiful and abundant country.
However, many wars broke out on earth.
A neighboring country tried to annex our country.
In order to save our country...
my father decided to move the country beneath the ocean.
That was thanks to help from the scientists from all over the world.
Thus our country sunk to the seabed.
After that the land world was ruined by wars.
The history is about to repeat itself.
This country is in the different dimension than the land world.
So the time passes slowly here.
We are watching how the world's changing from beneath the ocean.
But we don't want to be involved into any conflicts...
Don't worry.
We will create the world of peace.
We have Doraemon with us, to ensure that...
Yes!
Right. You kids' are the future of the land world.
Please create a peaceful and prosperous land world.
I will be watching your world from right here.
Leave it to us.
I but have an only request.
Please promise me that you'll never tell...
a word about our country, to anyone in your world.
Then our homework would be in vain.
How disappointing!
But... you haven't gifted us a Pandora's Box. Why?
I trust you children, so I won't gift you such horrible device.
Great.
Good bye.
Farewell!
I prefer this world after all!
Even though it's a fairy tale, its' reality sure is hard to accept.
Let's go home!
What if the Time Machine is broken, and we couldn't go back to our time?
Hey, don't scare us!
It really is gone!
The entrance of the Time Machine has disappeared.
It was here, I'm sure.
Then what about us...
We can't go home?
Again?
Your gadgets are always like that!
Not really...!!!
Then what?
I don't know either.
Mum.
It is useless to cry.
There must be humans living in 1049.
Anyway, let's find some house.
There is no baseball in this era.
And no TV neither!
No shower neither...
Our Mum's must be worried!
I'll have to do something!
Still we can't find any house at all.
It is dark, Doraemon!
Walk faster, Doraemon!
What now?
Look!
We are saved!
Hey!
What are you kids doing here at this late?
Mr. Cop, what year is it now?
It's now 1985. But why?
Yay, we are saved!
What is wrong with these kids?
We stayed 4 days in the Palace of the Dragon King...
...while in the land world, 800 years have been passed.
i understand now!
Whatever.
Go home quickly.
Yes, sir.
Strange kids.
We're back home!
Hey, kids front of the TV screen...!
Please make sure to keep the secret of Princess Oto to yourself only...
Promise me that you will...
Then good night.
Good night...
Huh?